

# **DANG PHUC THINH**

# **Backend Developer**

✓ dangphucthinha9@gmail.com

• 0935336719

Male

**29/04/1998** 

% https://www.fb.com/phucthinhdang ♥ Skype: dangphucthinha9@gmail.co

m or live:.cid.9b5ba3a78332aca5

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Desire to become a full-stack developer and work in a professional working environment promoting self-improvement. Participate in good reality and development projects that benefit society as well as promote company growth. From there, accumulate more experience, new knowledge, and skills to improve me.

#### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

## **MAJOR: INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

## **Danang University of Technology**

09/2016 - 05/2021

## **SKILLS**

C#

**REACT-JS** 

**PYTHON** 

HTML/CSS

SQL

**SWIFT** 

# **ACTIVITIES**

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

## **ENCLAVE**

06/2019 - now

Web DeveloperParticipate in various projects in the role of ASP.NET back-end developer, front-end developer (ReactJS).

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Enclave Vietnam

 Position: Backend developer

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

#### **USER MANAGER RESOURCE**

#### Web developer

09/2022 - now

- Description: Build a system for tracking and reporting customers at the casino
- Members: 6
- Role: Backend developer
- Language: ASP.NET 6.0, Entity Framework Core, AngularJs

# INBOX DETECTION AND RESPONSE

#### Web developer

05/2021 - 8/2022

- Description: System provides the solutions that automate email threat resolution in the user's inbox. If an attack gets through your current email security gateway, The system lets employees submit suspicious emails and then instantly routes those emails through machine learning filters—as well as expert human analysis—to check the email's true intent. In minutes the email is either verified or vanguished. All without help from IT, or enduser hassle.
- Members: 8
- Role: Backend and Frontend developer
- Language: C#, SQL Server, Vault, Jenkins, ReactJS,

# **REPORT SYSTEM**

### Web developer

01/2021 - 4/2021

• Duration: 2 years

- Description: Build a system for tracking and reporting in the factory

- Members: 15 - Role: FrontEnd

- Language: ASP.NET, EF core, SQL server, ReactJs

# **MMO TOOL**

#### Freelancer

05/2022 - 03/2023

- Description: A tool that is used for auto-watch videos and push channels to trend
- Members: 10
- Role: Backend developer
- Language: ASP.NET 6.0, Entity Framework Core, ReactJS

## **DIAMENT**

## Freelancer

09/2021 - 9/2021

- Description: API for APP and management website

- Members: 5- Role: Frontend

- Language: ReactJS